Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
And thus a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting.
Either way, I'm feeling alive!
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
Raise your flag up high.
Hail a brand new dawn.
Blaze across the sky.
Time to journey on.
On your mark.
Camel of other things.
We're on Earth, a legendary.
Hooray!
If you can show your breath,
Then we'll make some waves.
We run our daunted.
Ain't no beginners.
Cause if you're wanted,
Then you're a winner.
For we are on the cruise,
And freedom is the only rule.
Fearless night and day.
Cause that's just our way.
Find one piece.
I'll be the first.
I've heard it be so bad.
I could burst.
It's all this real.
It must be cause my hand's on a wheel.
I'm done playing, feel it's waiting.
In a world I'm feeling alive.
But I'll be loud.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We have come so far.
Gotta make it to the end.
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind!
I've always got your back, my friend.
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward.
Dreaming from the very
first day I'd make my name.
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed?
I'm done playing through with the wave.
In every world I'm feeling alive.
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We go.
Those officers were like
demons straight out of hell.
But they were a joke to the Straw Hats.
I'm glad they're on our side.
Heads up, fish people!
Eyes on the sky!
Danger's on the way down!
It's one on Sabo!
Those fours are flat!
Could have dropped him in a
place with less people, dumbass.
Shut it!
Keep complaining and I'll
drop the next giant on you!
That was downright amazing, Sanji!
Hey Chopper, you mind shrinking down some?
You're totally upstaging
my giant robot here.
Franky, that beam was so cool!
Are you serious?
That robot was utterly useless.
That reminds me.
Nami?
What is it?
You should really wear a miniskirt.
Stop it!
I can't really read my dad?
Well done.
Expected no less from Luffy's crew.
Wait.
There's an Owa!
The Owa's right above us!
It's gonna crush every last one of us.
We gotta get out of here!
Neptune's army might trap us in the plaza.
If we don't?
We can make it!
Those psycho officers can't stop us now.
Are you okay?
Oh no, are we too late?
Please do something Stop that thing!
Straw Hat!
Straw Hat is still fighting!
He's not giving up yet!
I can hardly believe what I'm seeing!
He still has strength length!
He's attacking the Noah!
It's breaking apart!
We'll be alright if he can
obliterate it before it crashes,
but if he's unable to,
then we're all doomed!
It will be the end for Fishman Island.
Give it everything you got, Lupi!
You got it!
Are you down here?
Come on, you can do it!
I believe in you.
Make it happen, Straw Hat!
We're rooting for you down here!
We know you can do it!
Keep it up, Straw Hat!
You may be a human but you've
got all of our support!
We ain't running nowhere!
Go Straw Hacks!
We all believe in you!
We save our country, Straw Hacks!
Save us all!
Tear it apart, Straw Hacks!
We don't need that ship anymore!
Straw Hacks!
No!
Snowhead!
Snowhead! Snowhead!
Stop that tower!
Destroy it!
Terror it to bits!
Wreck it all!
Wait, Lucy!
The moon is opening up again! J-Box!
You want to help?
Stay back and watch!
All that matters now with speed,
carry the damn thing apart!
Stop, you dumb shit!
Stop falling!
I'm sorry that this had to happen, Father.
Destroying the Noah?
It's the only thing to be done.
We're losing the ship of promise!
But what can be done?
My people's lives are more important.
Still, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I cannot keep the promise.
Joy Boy!
You may stop.
Who's there?
Enough, Luffy!
You can't do this!
You have to stop!
You're going to kill yourself!
Move with me, Hachi!
I have to save the island!
It's so tight now!
It's not alright!
Everyone's gonna die if I don't!
Will you just look?
The Noah stopped!
The sea kinks, but why?
You're angry!
I don't like it when you yell at me!
Hey!
We've got bigger problems to deal with!
I don't know what this means,
but I think it's a good thing.
They stopped it.
Somehow, the Noah's not falling.
What in the hell is happening?
Are you seeing this?
Did the Sea King seriously stop the Noah?
Oh, Luffy!
You're losing so much
blood from that wound!
We need to get you to a doctor!
Yeah, well, it's okay, really.
Just as long as the ship is stopped.
I'm just glad everyone is safe now.
Help me!
He'll be alright.
I gotta admit, that there
is one hell of a human.
Yeah, to say the least, he
sure is strong, isn't he?
Even if we had been late, the
island would have been saved,
at the cost of the Noah being
completely destroyed, of course.
Well, it's a good thing
we did make it then.
I sure am glad that Princess Shirahoshi
called out to us like that, just in time.
But I didn't do anything at all.
I was just sad.
Not quite.
Your will and the will of the human
echoed as one becoming a wish.
A prayer to us.
Your desire to save your people was so
strong, and we all heard it loud and clear.
You're not nearly as
helpless as you think.
The power of the Sea
Kingdoms is yours as well.
If you are in need, then
we shall heed your call.
People of the Kingdom.
I'm not sure what just happened here.
I'm not even sure if I can describe it.
But, whatever it was, it happened.
The Noah, it's been stopped!
And it's damaged, but not destroyed.
Frishman Island has been saved!
I knew Straw Hat would save us!
Thank you.
Princess Shirahoshi,
you can't imagine how long we see kings
waited for you to be born into this world.
Waited for me?
This vessel was designed for
us to pull it, can't you tell?
This responsibility has been passed
down for as long as anyone can remember.
Then, is that the reason
why the Noah is so large?
Worse.
Our queen appears once
every several centuries,
though we do not know why she
always takes the form of a mermaid.
It's strange.
I wonder.
But we do know that ever
since you were born,
you have been our exalted queen.
Is she? Yes.
I don't understand it, but I think...
Our sister is speaking with the Sea Kings.
Incredible.
You're not going to believe this, sir,
but a bunch of Sea Kings just showed up
out of the blue and they took hold of it.
And I'm not sure I understand
what they're saying, sir.
But I guess they stepped
in because they wanted
to stop Luffy from smashing
the Noah to pieces.
For whatever reason, that shit must
be really important to them, too.
Your Majesty.
Hmm.
Sea kings.
So, it's finally awakened.
The power that can
destroy this entire world.
Look!
The bubble's being absorbed
by the island bit by bit.
He won't survive in the deep sea.
Quickly, Shirahoshi.
You must retrieve him.
if i didn't know better i'd
say that the human wearing
the hat was able to hear
us as well I doubt that.
It has happened before.
Not so long ago.
Oh, I remember.
Rayleigh, did you hear
that voice just now?
You're crazy.
There's obviously nobody down here.
Who's there?
Why am I hearing strange voices
at the bottom of the sea?
Show yourself now!
Quite mysterious.
Quite mysterious indeed.
Ah!
Seeking's you!
And they're pulling the Noah! Ah!
Please don't eat me!
The Noah is crumbling.
Can it be saved?
Can it serve its purpose?
Well, I believe it could be
saved if we had their help.
However, this is a different age.
Then can it be repaired?
I certainly hope so.
The appointed time is approaching.
Minister of the Left, sir, we have a
report from inside the Ryugu palace.
What's happening?
Well, the good news is we've located
all the mermaids who were kidnapped.
It turns out they're right
here on the premises.
Oh, thank goodness!
Please tell me they're all right.
Yes, they said they're still
feeling a bit disoriented,
sir, but they do remember
what the culprit looked like.
Bad news is the treasure
chamber's been wiped clean.
They took it all down to the last piece.
It's awful.
We even lost the tomate box, sir.
Your Majesty,
someone seems to have robbed
us during the commotion.
Stolen treasures do not concern us.
Now, not moments ago, we
nearly lost our entire kingdom.
The best thing to do at present is tell
the citizens that the mermaids are safe.
The damage may be done, but we still
need to clear the Straw Hats' names.
We must do the right thing.
I won't hesitate to shoot
you if you try to get a worm.
Am I clear?
Never mind.
You're gonna kill us boss team day.
Come on, please.
You gotta let us out of
here We only did this
stuff cuz we were scared
of holding in his crib.
We are humans You know this fish man
civil war things got nothing to do
with us besides tourism from human
pirates is good for their economy So, uh,
yeah, come on man.
Just let us go, please the punishment
may not be as terrible as you think
Let us wait to hear the
royal family's decision.
There is one fact of which we must make
all of you aware the mermaids are safe.
And as for the Straw Hats they
were not involved in any way.
We humbly admit that
mistakes were made in our
investigation for the
unrest that this has caused.
We must apologize you know i never
doubted the Straw Hats for a second.
I knew it wasn't them from the start.
I just didn't want to say anything.
Drop the app.
We're all to blame. Look at us.
We didn't trust them for a second.
Nah, we believed them
all along, right? Yeah.
Hey, that's not true.
Don't say that.
I heard what you said. Me too.
Admit it.
We all believed the Straw
Hats were responsible.
We judged them.
Just because they were humans.
Yeah, you're right.
We've always been like that.
I feel awful.
Super!
Look at that!
It's just like mine!
Yeah, only cooler!
It's because I use
Monster Point, that's all.
That one wears me out.
I won't be able to walk for a few hours,
but I can still treat your injuries,
slowly.
Now those hurt, let me take a look.
Worry about yourself first.
It looks like everyone here is fine
except for me after all that fighting.
I need to rest my head, too Only
your lap can heal me, please
Rest it up your ass instead
if Robin wants me to what?
Luffy
The Princes are here!
It's Hordean Deccan!
We've returned.
We're sorry we worried you, father.
All that matters is that you're safe.
Hear me, citizens!
There is no need to fear!
Never again will these villains
cause trouble for our kingdom!
Whoa!
Has this been a crazy day or what?
What a terrible monster that is!
And to think he was right
here in our neighborhood.
Captain Horton, what happened to you?
We shouted who's boss!
Huh?
I know that voice.
That's the princess!
Seems she's okay!
Look, it's the princess
and Straw Hat Luffy!
Someone help!
I don't know what to do!
I hope you won't stop bleeding!
I'm afraid he's going to die!
Luffy's so brave, he could've
died out there, fighting for us!
Hope he's okay.
This looks bad, but I've got a
few hemostatics here in my bag.
Thanks a lot, Robin? Sure!
Whoa, is that new form really
worth doing this every time?
Right, here we go.
Let me help you, Moon.
What?
What kind of doctor are you?
A little left, there.
Oh, doctor, tell me Luffy's
going to be alright?
He can stop the bleeding, but
he's lost an awful lot of blood.
He needs a donor.
Well, that's no good.
Luffy's the only one of us with type F.
So we can't do it?
There's got to be someone who can.
Somebody!
Help us!
I'm type F.
I'm the right type, but...
Papa, you're type F, right?
Well, I, uh...
Oh, right!
I forgot in this country there's actually
a law against donating blood to humans.
What?
What kind of law is that? It's cruel.
Aw, come on!
This guy just saved you!
I'd like to help but I'm afraid
my blood isn't tight enough.
It is red though!
Is that good enough?
That's not really how it works but thanks.
Princess Shiromoshi Wait a sec.
Maybe the human pirates could help it.
You can give him some of my blood.
It's type f.
Take as much as you need.
Wow.
Really thanks, Jimbae!
Wait but the law...
what of it?
I'm a pirate boss, Jimbae.
You're the boss, Jimbae!
Wonderful!
Wait, Jimbae!
If you...
it's all right.
What makes it so wrong?
It's precisely that kind of thinking
that caused this to begin with.
It might sting a little, okay?
I can take it.
If you harm someone...
Or,
if someone harms you,
the same red
blood is spilled.
And this tube through
which that blood flows,
small and fragile though it is,
provides a pathway,
through
the prejudice
that divides us,
and
the
conflicts
that we create.
as though they were never there at all.
And more than any fleeting
dream or fantasy could,
this path can guide us to the surface?
into the warm light of the sun.
Team Bay Luffy It scared me.
Luffy
You rascal!
So you were awake?
He's okay!
Yay, Reef!
You see, mother?
We made it.
Back to Saru.
Hey, Zunbei.
I want you to join my crew.
The royal family has reached a decision!
Freak up!
Finally free!
Screw you, Wardy!
Now who's in chains?
Sorry that I was going to be a
slave for the rest of my life.
Thank you, Straw Hats.
I swear I'll repay you someday!
After I become king of the pirates? What?
That's a bit ambitious Hey,
what's wrong with having trees?
Oh, pirates, I can set
sail for the new world?
Your majesty Are you sure it's wise
to release Hody's human slaves?
We can't let such fears turn
us into something we're not.
This island has always been a welcoming,
safe place for pirates to rest.
And these humans never meant
us any deliberate harm.
We have no right to imprison them.
Now then, as for the rest
of the new Fishman Pirates?
That's a different story.
Don't cut my head off!
Please bear our lives.
Your Highness, really?
We didn't know anything about
Heart killing the Queen.
They lied to us.
We got duped by a bunch of lunatics.
That's the truth!
It's Horty's fault.
We're not responsible.
From here on?
I officially order you all to
live here on the main island.
Hang on!
You're telling us to
live law-abiding lives?
It could be a lot worse,
better than working for Heart.
Come on!
You can't be serious, King!
We don't want them living among us!
We won't feel safe to let our
kids walk down the street!
To clarify,
you will serve your time, of course,
and you will work under
the supervision of my army.
I will provide you all with gainful
employment to use up all that energy of yours.
And from this day forward,
the Fishman District will be sealed
off and all entry prohibited.
The dark side of the
Fishman had been exposed,
along with the true
killer of Queen Otohime.
The conspirator, Heart Jones, attempted
to seize control of Fishman Island.
But he failed.
All thanks to a band of
human pirates who happened
to be passing through
at just the right time.
Hey, have you seen Straw Hat Luffy around?
Well, he, um, absconded.
Why did you leave the plaza
without saying anything?
Are you running away?
We're not too big on attention.
You saw how many spectators we
had watching us fight down there.
If we stick around, they'd just treat
us like heroes or some dumb crap.
Just the thought of it
makes me want to puke.
But why?
Isn't it a good thing to
be the hero of a nation?
Listen up.
I'll spell it out for you.
A man who shares his sake with
other people, now that's a hero.
But I want it all for myself.
Keep your damn sake!
And stop putting dumb ideas in her head!
Why won't you join us, Deep Bay?
I know you've got adventure in your blood!
Come on, it'll be the most
fun you've ever had, I swear!
He's right!
Crew up with us, boss!
It'd be awesome to have
a former warlord with us!
And helpful!
Luffy could take a little break!
I told you, it's impossible
for me to join you now.
But I am still grateful.
It is an honor that you asked.
I am certain that it would be the adventure
of my life to sail the sea with you all.
But I am afraid I don't have the
luxury to indulge in such pleasures.
I have responsibilities
that I must fulfill.
And I put them off long enough as it is.
Once I've seen, to my duties.
When I'm free from my sworn obligations.
I promise I'll set sail and seek you out!
No matter where you may be.
And if you haven't changed your mind.
And still wish for me to
become a member of your crew.
Well, I'll gladly take
you up on your offer then.
If you see fit to have me?
You better keep that promise.
Whoa, hey.
A man's got to do what a man's got to do.
Give him some time, Captain.
He's really taken with Jean-Bang.
Luffy made it clear you're worth the wait.
So if you need some me time, you got it.
That is very gracious of you.
So what are we doing next? Where to?
A new world, right?
What?
You're leaving just like that?
I haven't thanked you properly.
It's not fair.
Why, we've hardly spoken at all.
Okay, it's settled then.
Let's stay at the Mermaid
Cafe a whole week.
You got some kind of nosebleed death wish?
Sounds fun, though.
Hey, hold on!
Who's that?
Looks like he must be a
soldier from Neptune's army.
Straw Hat, please wait just a moment.
Okay, Your Majesty.
They're right here and listening.
Well done.
Luffy, my friend, why did
you leave in such a rush?
I wanted to thank you.
I don't want to be
treated like a damn hero.
Yes, I can appreciate that,
but at least let me throw you the
banquet that we originally set to enjoy.
Banquet? Sure!
Let's go pick up Pachi and Kuma.
And with Neptune's official decree
the fishman district was sealed off
As for the fate of Heart his
officers of the new fishman pirates
and Vanderdecken They were all
locked away within the prison tower
Go for it Kraken take him far away what
I'm assuming you may not fit in our
prison cells but you are forbidden
from ever entering this country again!
Did you catch some? Yeah!
Good job, kids.
Let's get them prepared and
take them up to the palace.
This banquet for the Straw Hats is
going to be a night to remember.
That's for sure.
They'll get their fill of
sea monster meat, no doubt.
And we're bringing all the
snacks and cakes we can.
Heard they got bottomless stomachs.
We better back all of it.
And every cask of sake we've got, they're
drinking nothing but the best tonight.
Welcome to the palace, Straw Hats.
I'm honored you've chosen to join us,
and I'm eager to speak with
you during the banquet.
The Long Flounders will be
arriving to take you to the hall.
Whoa, those are some huge
rays. They're flukes.
But I thought he just
called them flounders.
We're underwater?
It's so dark.
So surreal.
They're really letting us in.
I'm kind of nervous.
Phew, it's the royal palace.
This is nuts.
Uh, hey, where's the meat?
Look, the heroes have arrived.
Whoa, look at all the soldiers down there.
We aren't anybody's damn heroes.
Just want to eat the meat.
Yeah, and drink all of your sake, too.
First look at the stage!
This way! You see?
Stage?
We proudly present the greatest
diva of the deep sea, Marina Napol!
And her backing band,
the Swing Jazz Orchestra!
Wow!
She is the voice of an angel!
It's proper!
Yeah!
Seek it, girl!
You're rocking my soul
right out of this world!
Now, please welcome our special gets.
Wait, is it?
Their beauty has stolen the breath of
countless sailors and pirates alike.
The Mermaid Cafe
Dancers !" Be right!
Doin' die!
No picture in the world
could capture their beauty.
Oh, sugar touched the sea water.
Uh-oh.
It's a fish.
Katie?
It's me.
I'm so glad you're okay.
Yes, now we're talking.
Wouldn't be a banquet without it.
Sweet, me first, lady.
That's everything I dreamed it would be.
Thank you. Thank you.
Down here, mermaids.
Oh my, thank you.
Peace to peace. To peace.
Now, drink them!
There's plenty more where that came from.
I'm dying to!
Fungie, go!
Don't get so carried away, all right?
But first, you will listen as
I briefly express my gratitude.
Oh, Father.
Yeah, I know. Cheers! Cheers!
Cheers indeed.
Let's forget the speech.
Hey, you guys! Cheers! Cheers!
It's quite excellent.
Does it have something
to do with the water?
Oh, you're a kind of silly
old lady, aren't you?
Fill her up! What?
Don't look so shocked.
It's empty, isn't it?
That is some real tolerance.
My face is a robot.
The party is rocking.
Shit, shit, baby.
The beat is dropping.
God I mean, come dance with Ricky!
I'm dancing!
Yeah.
Oh.
Hello, pirate girl.
You wanted to speak with me?
I apologize, but this seemed like my
only chance to get you alone. What?
Now listen here, I'm very flattered, but
I swore to love my wife Otohime forever.
She might be dead, but I
must honor the oath I made.
I'd like to know who Joy Boy is. Hmm?
I saw it myself, the
poneglyph in the sea forest.
Just who exactly is he apologizing to?
Are you telling me that you can read it?
I'm a survivor of Ohara.
You don't have to tell me
anything if you prefer.
No.
I will gladly tell you everything I know.
You've proven yourself trustworthy.
What I know of Joy Boy is that
he was a person from above the
sea who lived during the time of
the hundred year void which is to
say more than 800 years ago the
message you read he wrote to a
mermaid princess who lived on this
island during that time period
it is a letter of apology
for failing to keep
the promise he made to
this island what promise
i'm afraid that i don't know
the specific details but
according to the legend it
said that somebody will come to
fulfill it someday on behalf
of joy boy at least that's the
story that's been passed down
through our royal family and
we firmly believe that
this day will come so we've
continued to look after the
noah for generations just as we
promised him and when the time
arrives the noah will finally
be put to its intended use
whatever that may be i see now i
couldn't help but overhear
that the half-destroyed noah
was taken to the sea forest
after the battle came to an
end today by the sea kings that
is if joy boy truly planned
to use the noah i have to
wonder if he had control of the
sea kings no it was actually
the former mermaid princess
who possessed that fearsome
power that's what i thought and
now Shirahoshi has the same
ability she has for quite some
time But it seems that it did
not fully awaken until today.
I can't say that I'm terribly pleased.
I know how you feel.
Two years ago,
up in Shandora, I read a poneglyph that
located one of the ancient weapons.
All signs indicated this very island.
This mermaid princess who lived
during the same time as Joy Boy.
She was known by another
name as well wasn't she.
And now Shirahoshi
possesses the same power
so she will come to
inherit the same name too.
A terrible thing for a father to hear but.
She is the ancient weapon.
Poseidon.